kalaharilifestyle.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Kalahari Lifestyle

Kalahari Pty Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy applies to all web pages related to this website, as well as social media pages and any other verified web properties associated with Kalahari Pty Ltd (“properties”). All of the information gathered via these Properties (“data”) is used to identify users that use this site and/or interact with our brand online.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your personally identifiable information.

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. You also agree not to: circumvent, remove, alter, deactivate, degrade or thwart any of the content protections on this site; use any robot, spider, scraper or other automated means to access this site; decompile, reverse engineer or disassemble any software or other products or processes accessible through this site; insert any code or product or manipulate the content of this site in any way; or, use any data mining, data gathering or extraction method. In addition, you agree not to upload, post, e-mail or otherwise send or transmit any material designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment associated with this site, including any software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not make use of this site.

  1. What personal information do we collect?

This site uses Google Analytics tracking to collect data about your visit, including: duration, device used, pages visited, actions taken, geographical location (region, country and city), age (generalised), gender, date, time of day, the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. Google Analytics does not yield any piece of information that can be used in isolation to identify you personally.

When ordering from us, completing a contact form, or subscribing to our newsletter, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other personal details.

You may elect (at your sole discretion) to enter your personal information into a form embedded on this site. Such information can be used to identify you personally and typically includes: your names, date of birth, contact information, address information and employment information. Likewise, should you enter into any competition run by the Providers, either via this site or one of our other Properties, you acknowledge that you do so knowingly and at your own discretion.

  2. How do we use of information that is collected?

This information is used to help improve the site, analyse trends, and further administer this site. We may also use this information internally to improve our products and services. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our website. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone else.

Information that you enter into a contact form on this website will be used to contact you and assist with any enquiry that is raised through that form. In addition, information that you enter into a newsletter subscription form on this website will be used to send you newsletter updates. Please see the section titled ‘Communication Preferences’ in our Website Terms of Use for further details.

Your contact details will not be automatically added to our marketing communication database. Instead, the providers make use of double opt-in mechanisms to guarantee that all persons who receive marketing communication from Kalahari Pty Ltd have explicitly opted in to do so. This form of consent is unambiguous, specific and given freely. You can withdraw your consent at any time by following the instructions provided in these communications.

Data that is collected will not be used for any purpose other than that which is stated in these terms.

  3. Do we use cookies?

Yes. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more information.

  4. Storage of information

The providers endeavour to store all data securely at all times. Data may be stored locally and/or using trusted, verified tools offered by third-party providers. Every effort is made to ensure data safety (including, but not limited to: enforcement of strong password policies, encryption, activity notifications, database maintenance, off-site back-up and automatic back-up). By choosing to use and/or enter your information on this website, you acknowledge and agree that the providers will not be held responsible for any breach or similar lapse in security on the part of third-party providers whose tools are used to store or process data, howsoever caused.

Please refer back to this policy regularly.

  5. Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  6. Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

  7. CAN-SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them. We collect your email address in order to send you newsletters and promotional emails about our products and services. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info@kalaharistyle.com and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy please contact us.

  8. Notes

Kalahari Pty Ltd may from time to time change this Privacy Policy and other terms of service, or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice.

  9. Data Protection Officer

Information gathered through Kalahari Pty Ltd’ web properties is processed by Kalahari Pty Ltd. Please direct any concerns or enquiries regarding this Privacy Policy to :

Email: info@kalaharistyle.com

Phone: + 27 (0) 11 656 1122
